Viewers all over the world, if you honestly examine your heart in light of God's Word,
you will discover that there is a spirit of unforgiveness, a spirit of anger,
a spirit of bitterness, a spirit of jealousy, a spirit of envy
and such a spirit breaks our communion with God, our relationship with God.
It opens the door to whatever situation you are in now.
You say, "I have sickness." What is the root of sickness? Unforgiveness.
Hardship - what is the root of hardship? Envy, jealousy, anger.
That is the route, the road to get to you.
Are you sick, facing hardship, poverty, loneliness, rejection?
Whatever you are facing, the route of those things is unforgiveness, envy, jealousy, bitterness.
These are the routes.
You don't need the enemy to attack you; once you have these, you have attacked yourself.
Unforgivingness, envy, jealousy, bitterness, strife, and hatred
open the door to whatever you are in.
I release you from the pain of the past.
I release you from that unforgiving spirit, that bitterness, envy, jealousy.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
Father, release your children, in the name of Jesus!
Release Your children, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
Every unclean spirit in your career,
every unclean spirit in your life,
every unclean spirit - leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
God has spoken - rejoice!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
I cover you with the Blood of Jesus!
I seal you with the Blood of Jesus!
Be covered with the Blood of Jesus!
Begin a new life!
A new beginning!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
A new beginning is a new life,
a new direction,
a new way.
A new beginning!
A new beginning, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
God has spoken, in Jesus' name!
I can sense God's healing touching you.
I can sense God's deliverance touching you, in Jesus' name!
Hear this: God has spoken!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name.
RV Robert Begier 23/04/2019